Guide to the Henry Noble MacCracken Papers, 1907 - circa 1968
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES I. TRUSTEES AND ADMINISTRATION, 1915-1946
  - Trustees and Administration, 1938-1941
    - Chaplain Committee (Folder 13.52)
    - Endowment Committee (Folder 13.53)
    - Endowment Committee (Folder 13.54)
    - Endowment Committee (Folder 13.55)
    - Committee on Investments and Finance: minutes (Folder 13.56)
    - Committee on Investments and Finance: minutes (Folder 13.57)
    - Committee on Investments and Finance (Folder 14.1)
    - Committee on Investments and Finance (Folder 14.2)
    - Committee on Investments and Finance (Folder 14.3)
    - Committee on Investments and Finance (Folder 14.4)
    - Committee on Investments and Finance (Folder 14.5)
    - Committee on Investments and Finance (Folder 14.6)
    - Joint Committee on Future Finance (Folder 14.7)
    - Committee on Future Enrollment of Joint Planning (Folder 14.8)
    - Committee on Long-Range Planning Committee (Folder 14.9)
    - Memorial Tablets Committee (Folder 14.10)
    - Committee on Nominations (Folder 14.11)
    - Publicity Committee of Summer Institute (Folder 14.12)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Life (Folder 14.13)
  - Trustees and Administration, 1941-1946
    - Executive Committee: minutes (Folder 14.14)
    - Executive Committee: correspondence (Folder 14.15)
    - Committee on Faculty Studies: minutes (Folder 14.16)
    - Faculty Studies Committee: correspondence (Folder 14.17)
    - Faculty Studies Committee: correspondence (Folder 14.18)
    - Budget for 1942-1943 (Folder 14.19)
    - Budget for 1942-1943 (Folder 14.20)
    - Budget for 1942-1943 (Folder 14.21)
    - Budget for 1942-1943 (Folder 14.22)
    - Budget for 1942-1943 (Folder 14.23)
    - Budget for 1942-1943 (Folder 14.24)
    - Budget for 1943-1944 (Folder 14.25)
    - Budget for 1943-1944 (Folder 14.26)
    - Budget for 1943-1944 (Folder 14.27)
    - Budget for 1943-1944 (Folder 14.28)
    - Budget for 1943-1944 (Folder 14.29)
    - Budget for 1944-1945 (Folder 14.30)
    - Budget for 1944-1945 (Folder 14.31)
    - Budget for 1944-1945 (Folder 14.32)
    - Budget for 1944-1945 (Folder 14.33)
    - Budget for 1944-1945 (Folder 14.34)
    - Budget for 1945-1946 (Folder 14.35)
    - Budget for 1945-1946 (Folder 14.36)
    - Budget for 1945-1946 (Folder 14.37)
    - Budget for 1945-1946 (Folder 14.38)
    - Salary Contingent Fund (Folder 14.39)
    - Comptroller-Salaries (Folder 14.40)
    - Comptroller-Salaries (Folder 14.41)
    - Comptroller (Folder 14.42)
    - Comptroller (Folder 14.43)
    - Comptroller (Folder 14.44)
    - Memorandum to the Executive Committee, 1946 (Folder 14.45)
    - Investments, Aug 1941-Sep 1943, 1 (Folder 15.1)
    - Investments, Aug 1941-Sep 1943, 2 (Folder 15.2)
    - Investments, Dec 1943-Sep 1946, 1 (Folder 15.3)
    - Investments, Dec 1943-Sep 1946, 2 (Folder 15.4)
    - Treasurer, 1 (Folder 15.5)
    - Treasurer, 2 (Folder 15.6)
    - Treasurer, 3 (Folder 15.7)
    - Department of Halls (Folder 15.8)
    - Mr. Henry Brown (Folder 15.9)
    - Mr. Downer (Folder 15.10)
    - General Manager, 1 (Folder 15.11)
    - General Manager, 2 (Folder 15.12)
    - General Manager, 3 (Folder 15.13)
    - General Manager, 4 (Folder 15.14)
    - Statute of Instruction, 1 (Folder 15.15)
    - Statute of Instruction, 2 (Folder 15.16)
    - Statute of Instruction, 3 (Folder 15.17)
    - Statute of Instruction, 4 (Folder 15.18)
  - V.C. 50th Anniversary; College Endowment 1915-17; College Reconstruction Fund 1918-1919
    - Faculty 50th Anniversary Committee, 1 (Folder 15.19)
    - Faculty 50th Anniversary Committee, 2 (Folder 15.20)
    - 50th Anniversary Publications (Folder 15.21)
    - A (Folder 15.22)
    - B (Folder 15.23)
    - C (Folder 15.24)
    - D (Folder 15.25)
    - E (Folder 15.26)
    - F (Folder 15.27)
    - G (Folder 15.28)
    - H (Folder 15.29)
    - I (Folder 15.30)
    - J (Folder 15.31)
    - K (Folder 15.32)
    - L (Folder 15.33)
    - M (Folder 15.34)
    - N (Folder 15.35)
    - P (Folder 15.36)
    - R (Folder 15.37)
    - S (Folder 15.38)
    - U (Folder 15.39)
    - V (Folder 15.40)
    - W (Folder 15.41)
    - Y (Folder 15.42)
    - Albany - Alumnae (Folder 15.43)
    - Chicago - Alumnae (Folder 15.44)
    - Class of 1900 - Mrs. H.G. Plum. Secretary (Folder 15.45)
    - Class of 1905 - H. Kenyon -Endowment (Folder 15.46)
    - Class of 1906 (Folder 15.47)
    - Class of 1907 (Folder 15.48)
    - Class of 1908 - L. Loyd, Sec'y - Endowment (Folder 15.49)
    - Class of 1910 (Folder 15.50)
    - Class of 1911 (Folder 15.51)
    - Class of 1913 (Folder 15.52)
    - Class of 1916 (Folder 15.53)
    - Cleveland Alumnae (Folder 15.54)
    - Cole Engravings, 1 (Folder 15.55)
    - Cole Engravings, 2 (Folder 15.56)
    - Denver Vassar Club (Folder 15.57)
    - Detroit Alumnae-Endowment (Folder 15.58)
    - Endowment Campaign Methods (Folder 15.59)
    - Endowment Committee-Alumnae, 1 (Folder 15.60)
    - Endowment Committee-Alumnae, 2 (Folder 15.61)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Correspondence (Folder 15.62)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Fund, 1 (Folder 15.63)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Fund, 2 (Folder 15.64)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Fund, 3 (Folder 15.65)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Fund, 4 (Folder 15.66)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Fund, 5 (Folder 15.67)
    - Former Students- Endowment (Folder 15.68)
    - New York Alumnae-Endowment (Folder 15.69)
    - Prospective Endowment, 1 (Folder 15.70)
    - Prospective Endowment, 2 (Folder 15.71)
    - St. Louis Club (Folder 15.72)
    - Undergraduates (Folder 15.73)
    - Wheeler, H.A. - Chairman, Parents' Committee (Folder 15.74)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 15.75)
    - B - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.1)
    - C - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.2)
    - D- Emergency Fund (Folder 16.3)
    - E- Emergency Fund (Folder 16.4)
    - H - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.5)
    - J- Emergency Fund (Folder 16.6)
    - K - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.7)
    - L - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.8)
    - M - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.9)
    - N - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.10)
    - O - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.11)
    - P - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.12)
    - R - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.13)
    - S - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.14)
    - T - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.15)
    - V - Emergency Fund (Folder 16.16)
    - W- Emergency Fund (Folder 16.17)
    - Reconstruction Fund-Misc., lists, etc., 1 (Folder 16.18)
    - Reconstruction Fund-Misc., lists, etc., 2 (Folder 16.19)
    - Emergency Fund Surplus (Folder 16.20)
- SERIES II. BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS, 1915-1949
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1915-1949
    - Acoustics (Folder 16.21)
    - College Architect-general, 1 (Folder 16.22)
    - College Architect-general, 2 (Folder 16.23)
    - Architects, 1 (Folder 16.24)
    - Architects, 2 (Folder 16.25)
    - Architects, 3 (Folder 16.26)
    - Architects, 4 (Folder 16.27)
    - Alumnae House, 1 (Folder 16.28)
    - Alumnae House, 2 (Folder 16.29)
    - Alumnae House, 3 (Folder 16.30)
    - Alumnae House, 4 (Folder 16.31)
    - Alumnae House, 5 (Folder 16.32)
    - Alumnae House, 6 (Folder 16.33)
    - Alumnae House, 7 (Folder 16.34)
    - Alumnae House, 8 (Folder 16.35)
    - Alumnae House, 9 (Folder 16.36)
    - Alumnae House, 10 (Folder 16.37)
    - Alumnae House, 11 (Folder 16.38)
    - Alumnae House, 12 (Folder 16.39)
    - Alumnae House, 13 (Folder 16.40)
    - Arboretum (Folder 16.41)
    - Architecture (Folder 16.42)
    - Architect: Appointment of new firm, 1937 (Folder 16.43)
    - Assembly Hall (Folder 16.44)
    - Aula (Folder 16.45)
    - Avery Hall, 1 (Folder 16.46)
    - Avery Hall, 2 (Folder 16.47)
    - Bakery, 1 (Folder 16.48)
    - Bakery, 2 (Folder 16.49)
    - Blodgett Hall (Folder 16.50)
    - Blodgett Hall, Jan 1, 1929- (Folder 16.51)
    - Blodgett Hall, Jan 1, 1929- (Folder 16.52)
    - Blodgett Hall, Jan 1, 1929- (Folder 16.53)
    - Blodgett Hall, Lists of Furnishings, 1 (Folder 16.54)
    - Blodgett Hall, Lists of Furnishings, 2 (Folder 16.55)
    - Browsing Room (Folder 16.56)
    - Buildings, 1 (Folder 16.57)
    - Buildings, 2 (Folder 16.58)
    - Buildings, 3 (Folder 16.59)
    - Buildings, 4 (Folder 16.60)
    - Candy Kitchen (Folder 16.61)
    - Chapel Building, 1 (Folder 17.1)
    - Chapel Building, 2 (Folder 17.2)
    - Chapel Building, 3 (Folder 17.3)
    - Chapel Building, 4 (Folder 17.4)
    - Chapel Building, 5 (Folder 17.5)
    - Chapel Organ, 1 (Folder 17.6)
    - Chapel Organ, 2 (Folder 17.7)
    - Chapel Organ, 3 (Folder 17.8)
    - Chapel Chimes (Folder 17.9)
    - Chapel Tower Room, 1 (Folder 17.10)
    - Chapel Tower Room, 2 (Folder 17.11)
    - Chapel Tower Room, 3 (Folder 17.12)
    - Chapel Tower Room, 4 (Folder 17.13)
    - Classical Museum (Folder 17.14)
    - Concrete Benches (Folder 17.15)
    - Classrooms (Folder 17.16)
    - Cushing Hall, 1 (Folder 17.17)
    - Cushing Hall, 2 (Folder 17.18)
    - Dean's House (Folder 17.19)
    - Diet Kitchen (Folder 17.20)
    - Dining Room - Treasurer (Folder 17.21)
    - Eleanor Conservatory (Folder 17.22)
    - Ely Hall (Folder 17.23)
    - Ely Hall (Folder 17.24)
    - "Exeter" Room (Folder 17.25)
    - Blodgett Hall - Through Dec 31, 1928 (Folder 17.26)
    - Blodgett Hall - Through Dec 31, 1928 (Folder 17.27)
    - Blodgett Hall - Through Dec 31, 1928 (Folder 17.28)
    - Beatrix Farrand - Landscape Gardener (Folder 17.29)
    - Faculty House (Folder 17.30)
    - Faculty House (Folder 17.31)
    - Faculty House (Folder 17.32)
    - Faculty House (Folder 17.33)
    - Faculty House (Folder 17.34)
    - Faculty House - Suggested Plans (Folder 17.35)
    - Trustees Executive Committee - Faculty Rooms (Folder 17.36)
    - Professor House (Folder 17.37)
    - Professor House (Folder 17.38)
    - Professor House (Folder 17.39)
    - Farm (Folder 17.40)
    - Treasurer - Fire Regulations (Folder 17.41)
    - Furniture (Folder 17.42)
    - 1882 Gateway (Folder 17.43)
    - Geology Dept. - Changes (Folder 17.44)
    - Golf Course (Folder 17.45)
    - Good Fellowship Clubhouse (Folder 17.46)
    - Greenhouses (Folder 17.47)
    - Grounds (Folder 17.48)
    - Grounds (Folder 17.49)
    - Grounds (Folder 17.50)
    - Grounds (Folder 17.51)
    - Gymnasium [i.e., Ely Hall] (Folder 17.52)
    - Heating Plant (Folder 17.53)
    - Head Warden's House (Folder 17.54)
    - Highways (Folder 17.55)
    - Ice Hockey Rink (Folder 17.56)
    - Ice Plant (Folder 18.1)
    - Indoor Garden (Folder 18.2)
    - Infirmary (Folder 18.3)
    - Insurance (Folder 18.4)
    - Interior Decorator (Folder 18.5)
    - Josselyn Hall Fire (Folder 18.6)
    - Kendrick House (Folder 18.7)
    - Lathrop Hall (Folder 18.8)
    - Library (Folder 18.9)
    - Library (Folder 18.10)
    - Library Addition - Development of Plans, Jan 1, 1935-June 30, 1936 (Folder 18.11)
    - Library Addition - Development of Plans, Jan 1, 1935-June 30, 1936 (Folder 18.12)
    - Library Addition - Development of Plans, July 1, 1936- (Folder 18.13)
    - Library Addition - Miscellaneous (Folder 18.14)
    - Library Addition - Dedication (Folder 18.15)
    - Library Addition - Building Companies (Folder 18.16)
    - Library Addition - Seminars (Folder 18.17)
    - Library - Shelving Estimates (Folder 18.18)
    - Library Addition - Lighting (Folder 18.19)
    - Library Furniture (Folder 18.20)
    - Library Addition - Mr. Kahu (Folder 18.21)
    - Library Addition - Landscaping (Folder 18.22)
    - Library Addition - Development of Plans, Nov 1, 1932-Dec 31, 1934 (Folder 18.23)
    - Library Addition - Development of Plans, Nov 1, 1932-Dec 31, 1934 (Folder 18.24)
    - Underhill Hall (Folder 18.25)
    - Library Addition - Development of Plans to Oct 31, 1932 (Folder 18.26)
    - Library Addition - Development of Plans to Oct 31, 1932 (Folder 18.27)
    - Lighting (Folder 18.28)
    - Lot Option (Folder 18.29)
    - Main Building (Folder 18.30)
    - Main Building (Folder 18.31)
    - Main Building - Alterations (Folder 18.32)
    - Main Building - Alterations (Folder 18.33)
    - Main Building - Fire (Folder 18.34)
    - Memorial Tablets - Companies (Folder 18.35)
    - Memorial Tablets - Companies (Folder 18.36)
    - Men's Club Room (Folder 18.37)
    - Metcalf House (Folder 18.38)
    - Metcalf Pavilion (Folder 18.39)
    - Museum (Folder 18.40)
    - Music Building (Folder 18.41)
    - New England Building (Folder 18.42)
    - New England Building (Folder 18.43)
    - North Hall Fire (Folder 18.44)
    - Officers' Parlor (Folder 18.45)
    - Offices (Folder 18.46)
    - Open-Air Theatre (Folder 19.1)
    - Phiel House (Folder 19.2)
    - Post Office (Folder 19.3)
    - Poultry Farm (Folder 19.4)
    - Physics Laboratory (Folder 19.5)
    - Physics Laboratory (Folder 19.6)
    - Physics Laboratory (Folder 19.7)
    - President's House (Folder 19.8)
    - President's House and Garage (Folder 19.9)
    - Psychology Laboratory (Folder 19.10)
    - Raymond Avenue [ see also 17.55 Highways] (Folder 19.11)
    - Raymond House (Folder 19.12)
    - Raymond House Decorations (Folder 19.13)
    - Raymond Reading Room (Folder 19.14)
    - Red Cross Room (Folder 19.15)
    - Riley House (Folder 19.16)
    - Rockefeller Hall (Folder 19.17)
    - Rockefeller Hall (Folder 19.18)
    - Sagar House (Folder 19.19)
    - Sanders Chemistry Laboratory (Folder 19.20)
    - Science Group (Folder 19.21)
    - Skinner Hall (Folder 19.22)
    - Social Museum (Folder 19.23)
    - Soundproofing (Folder 19.24)
    - Sound Projection Apparatus (Folder 19.25)
    - Sound Projection Apparatus (Folder 19.26)
    - Sound Studio (Folder 19.27)
    - Squash Court (Folder 19.28)
    - Students' Building (Folder 19.29)
    - Summer Use of Campus (Folder 19.30)
    - Swan Lane (Folder 19.31)
    - Swift Infirmary (Folder 19.32)
    - Swimming Pool (Folder 19.33)
    - Taking Pictures (Folder 19.34)
    - Taylor Hall (Folder 19.35)
    - Taylor Hall (Folder 19.36)
    - Tennis Courts (Folder 19.37)
    - Taxation (Folder 19.38)
    - Tennis Courts (Folder 19.39)
    - Training Camp Memorial (Folder 19.40)
    - Vassar Brothers Laboratory (Folder 19.41)
    - Warden's House (Folder 19.42)
    - Williams Hall (Folder 19.43)
    - Vassar Lake (Folder 19.44)
    - Williams Hall (Folder 19.45)
    - Williams Hall (Folder 19.46)
    - Williams Hall (Folder 19.47)
    - Williams Hall Building Committee (Folder 19.48)
    - Williams Hall - Wings 1 and 3 (Folder 19.49)
    - Williams Hall - Wings 1 and 3 (Folder 19.50)
    - Wing Farm (Folder 19.51)
    - Grey Wing Farm (Folder 19.52)
    - Wing Farm (Folder 19.53)
    - Worrall Farm (Folder 19.54)
- SERIES III. FACULTY, 1914-1945
  - FACULTY, 1914-1916
    - General, 1914-1916
      - Absences (Folder 19.55)
      - Acceptances (Folder 19.56)
      - Faculty Bibliography, 1914/1915 (Folder 19.57)
      - Faculty Bibliography, 1915/1916 (Folder 19.58)
      - Heads of Departments (Folder 19.59)
    - Faculty Committees, 1914-1916
      - Admission of Freshmen Committee (Folder 20.1)
      - Certificate Privilege Committee (Folder 20.2)
      - Codification of Faculty Rules (Folder 20.3)
      - College Publications Committee (Folder 20.4)
      - Committee to Appoint Committees (Folder 20.5)
      - Correlation of Freshmen Work (Folder 20.6)
      - Faculty Club, 1914/1915 (Folder 20.7)
      - Curriculum Committee - Faculty (Folder 20.8)
      - Intercollegiate Relations Committee (Folder 20.9)
      - Faculty Committee (Folder 20.10)
      - Convocation Committee (Folder 20.11)
      - Joint Committee (Folder 20.12)
      - Josselyn Hall Faculty (Folder 20.13)
      - Phi Beta Kappa Faculty (Folder 20.14)
      - Faculty Suffrage (Folder 20.15)
      - Twelve-Hour Privilege Room (Folder 20.16)
      - Committee on Curriculum (Folder 20.17)
      - Faculty Club (Folder 20.18)
      - Committee on Forms of Annual Reports (Folder 20.19)
      - Freshmen Board (Folder 20.20)
      - Committee on Intercollegiate Relations (Folder 20.21)
      - Joint Committee (Folder 20.22)
      - Student Records Committee (Folder 20.23)
      - Lecture Committee (Folder 20.24)
      - Library Committee (Folder 20.25)
      - Faculty Play - "Eastward Hoe" (Folder 20.26)
      - Student Records Committee (Folder 20.27)
      - Twelve-Hour Privilege Room Committee (Folder 20.28)
      - Count of Courses (Folder 20.29)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 20.30)
      - Absences - Faculty (Folder 20.31)
      - General Letters (Folder 20.32)
      - Heads of Departments (Folder 20.33)
      - Secretary of the Faculty (Folder 20.34)
      - Secretary of the Faculty (Folder 20.35)
      - Academic Suffrage (Folder 20.36)
      - Committee on Advanced Degrees (Folder 20.37)
      - Committee on Admissions (Folder 20.38)
      - 1915/16 Committees (Folder 20.39)
      - Botany Dept. Committee (Folder 20.40)
      - Calendar Committee (Folder 20.41)
      - Codification Committee (Folder 20.42)
      - Committee on Committees (Folder 20.43)
      - Committee to Confer with Trustees (Folder 20.44)
      - Convocation Committee (Folder 20.45)
      - Faculty for 1915/16 (Folder 20.46)
      - Faculty Budget, 1916/1917 (Folder 20.47)
      - Faculty Budget, 1916/1917 (Folder 20.48)
    - Art, 1914-1916
      - Reports (Folder 20.49)
      - Officers (Folder 20.50)
      - Officers (Folder 20.51)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.52)
      - Courses (Folder 20.53)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.54)
      - Re: Winifred Smith (Folder 20.55)
      - Reports (Folder 20.56)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.57)
      - Taylor Hall Art Gallery (Folder 20.58)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.59)
      - Courses (Folder 20.60)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.61)
    - Astronomy, 1914-1916
      - Officers (Folder 20.62)
      - Reports (Folder 20.63)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.64)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.65)
      - Officers (Folder 20.66)
      - Reports (Folder 20.67)
    - Bible, 1914-1916
      - Reports (Folder 20.68)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.69)
      - Courses (Folder 20.70)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.71)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.72)
      - Officers (Folder 20.73)
      - Reports (Folder 20.74)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.75)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.76)
    - Chemistry, 1914-1916
      - Officers (Folder 20.77)
      - Reports (Folder 20.78)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.79)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.80)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.81)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.82)
      - Officers (Folder 20.83)
      - Reports (Folder 20.84)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.85)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.86)
      - Courses (Folder 20.87)
    - Dean, 1914-1916
      - Officers (Folder 20.88)
      - Reports (Folder 20.89)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.90)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.91)
      - Officers (Folder 20.92)
      - Enrollment (Folder 20.93)
    - Economics, 1914-1916
      - Reports (Folder 20.94)
      - Officers (Folder 20.95)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.96)
      - Officers (Folder 20.97)
      - Reports (Folder 20.98)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.99)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.100)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.101)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.102)
    - English, 1914-1916
      - Appointments (Folder 20.103)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.104)
      - Reports (Folder 20.105)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.106)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.107)
      - Reports (Folder 20.108)
      - Officers (Folder 20.109)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.110)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.111)
      - Courses (Folder 20.112)
      - Courses (Folder 20.113)
      - Reports (Folder 20.114)
    - Folklore Foundation - Martha Beckwith: See English Department
    - French, 1914-1916
      - Officers (Folder 20.115)
      - Reports (Folder 20.116)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.117)
      - Re: Mrs. Conrow (Folder 20.118)
      - Re: Miss Fahnstock (Folder 20.119)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.120)
      - Officers (Folder 20.121)
      - Reports (Folder 20.122)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.123)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.124)
    - Geology, 1914-1916
      - Officers (Folder 20.125)
      - Reports (Folder 20.126)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.127)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.128)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.129)
      - Officers (Folder 20.130)
      - Reports (Folder 20.131)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.132)
    - German, 1914-1916
      - Appointments (Folder 20.133)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.134)
      - Reports (Folder 20.135)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.136)
      - Officers (Folder 20.137)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 20.138)
      - Officers (Folder 20.139)
      - Reports (Folder 20.140)
      - Appointments (Folder 20.141)
      - Conferences (Folder 20.142)
      - Courses (Folder 20.143)
      - Officers (Folder 21.1)
      - Reports (Folder 21.2)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.3)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 21.4)
      - Officers (Folder 21.5)
      - Reports (Folder 21.6)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.7)
    - History, 1914-1916
      - Officers (Folder 21.8)
      - Reports (Folder 21.9)
      - Courses (Folder 21.10)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.11)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.12)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 21.13)
      - Officers (Folder 21.14)
      - Reports (Folder 21.15)
    - Italian and Spanish, 1914-1916
      - Report - Romance Language (Folder 21.16)
      - Applications and Recommendations - Italian and Spanish (Folder 21.17)
      - Appointments (Folder 21.18)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.19)
      - Courses (Folder 21.20)
      - Officers (Folder 21.21)
      - Reports (Folder 21.22)
    - Latin, 1914-1916
      - Appointments (Folder 21.23)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.24)
      - Officers (Folder 21.25)
      - Reports (Folder 21.26)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 21.27)
      - Appointments (Folder 21.28)
      - Officers (Folder 21.29)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.30)
      - Reports: Library (Folder 21.31)
      - Appointments (Folder 21.32)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.33)
      - Donations (Folder 21.34)
      - Library Fund (Folder 21.35)
      - Officers (Folder 21.36)
      - Reports (Folder 21.37)
      - Officers (Folder 21.38)
      - Appointments (Folder 21.39)
      - Reports (Folder 21.40)
    - Mathematics, 1914-1916
      - Officers (Folder 21.41)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.42)
      - Reports (Folder 21.43)
      - Re: Miss Richardson (Folder 21.44)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 21.45)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.46)
      - Officers (Folder 21.47)
      - Reports (Folder 21.48)
    - Music, 1914-1916
      - Appointments (Folder 21.49)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 21.50)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.51)
      - Gifts (Folder 21.52)
      - Officers (Folder 21.53)
      - Reports (Folder 21.54)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 21.55)
      - Appointments (Folder 21.56)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.57)
      - Officers (Folder 21.58)
      - Reports (Folder 21.59)
    - Philosophy, 1914-1916
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 21.60)
      - Appointments (Folder 21.61)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.62)
      - Courses (Folder 21.63)
      - Officers (Folder 21.64)
      - Re: Dr. Elkus (Folder 21.65)
      - Reports (Folder 21.66)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 21.67)
      - Appointments (Folder 21.68)
      - Conferences (Folder 21.69)
      - Courses (Folder 21.70)
      - Officers (Folder 21.71)
      - Reports (Folder 21.72)
      - Suggestions for 1915/1916 (Folder 21.73)
    - Physical Training, 1914-1916